Damn Lewes
You have a secret feed
And didn't tell me earlier
Holding out on me
Once I steal the recipe
And fatten up my frogs
Your multimillion order will be mine
Why are you back
Lewes
I was wrong before
I'm here today to apologize
What are you plotting now
Don't always think the worst of me
Let's talk inside
Let's just talk here
The farm is a restricted area
No outsiders allowed
Brother-in-law
I borrowed from a loan shark
The interest gets higher every day
If I can't sell this batch of frogs
at a good price
I'm dead meat
You're the only one who can help me now
How do you want me to help you
I knew you
Value loyalty the most
And wouldn't abandon me
How about this
Brother-in-law
I heard you have a secret feed
That makes the frogs grow big and fat
Can you give me the recipe
I'll pay for it
The recipe took me two years
And hundreds of tests to develop
I've already patented it
It's not for sale
If you're here for this
You can leave now
Hey brother-in-law
I don't want the recipe
Can I just buy your feed
Sell me the finished product
And I'll feed them myself
Daniel
How you treated me before
You might have forgotten
but I haven't
I won't sell you the feed
Just leave
You
Fine
You just wait
This order will definitely be
mine
Wait